JESUS ROSALES

Email: jrosales6213@gmail.com Phone: 951-443-9616 <u>GitHub</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Website</u>

SUMMARY

A motivated, self-starting, and collaborative Junior Software Engineer with over 8 years of public-school experience seeking a Front-End Developer role. I have a passion for contributing to a representative industry and creating mobile first design websites and web applications.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Recall Inspector

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, React strap, API - NHTSA, database, Netlify Source Code | Demo

Aftershock

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Google Maps Visualizing Data, API - USGS, Netlify Source Code | Demo

Portfolio Website

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Netlify Source Code | Demo

EXPERIENCE

August 2014 - Present

Job Coach / Transition Specialist – Val Verde Unified School District

- Collect vocational data during trainings.
- Automated logs, schedules, and budget tracking data collection.
- Establish relationships with local businesses.
- Network with Community to find jobs and resources for adults with disabilities.

January 2012 – January 2016

Rosales Carpet Cleaning - Self Employed

- Negotiate with customers and vendors to achieve best prices.
- Schedule appointments, take inventory on supplies, routine maintenance on machine.
- Visit Customers, potential clients, and network with others to grow the business.
- Keep track of outgoing and incoming business expenses.

TECHNICAL COMPENTENCIES LANGUAGES

- HTML
- JAVASCRIPT

FRAMEWORKS

- REACT
- NODE
- EXPRESS

LIBRARIES

- REDUX
- MONGOOSE

DATABASES

MONGODB

TOOLS

- POSTMAN
- REST API

STYLING

- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- REACTSTRAP

VERSION CONTROL

- GIT
- GIT HUB

DEPLOYMENT

- NETLIFY
- HEROKU

EDUCATION

Nucamp Coding Bootcamp – August 2021 – January 2022

22 Week Bootcamp focused on Full Stack Web and Mobile App Development